[growls]
[wind howling]
[howling]
NETFLIX PRESENTS
[clock ticking]
[distant squeaking]
[clock ticking continues]
[woman 1] Yeah?
[man] Zoom in. Zoom in a bit. A bit more.
Jerzy, I can't hear anything!
[chatter quiets down]
[woman 2] Excuse me, can I ask you
to make the prompter font bigger?
[woman 1] We are eleven seconds behind.
[sighs]
Welcome to the final TV call-in contest
this year and this millennium.
Let us remind you of the prizes
the lucky winner will get.
[woman 1] More celebration,
smile and change your stance.
We will all together welcome the year 2000
on this square which is so important…
[reporter] This year's igloo
was over three meters tall.
The children were building it
for a few hours each day over two days.
It's just a way to… fill some time
over the winter break, isn't it?
Well, we want to do something,
like, incredible.
[clock ticking]
[unsettling music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[man ] Hello.
-Stop, stop, stop!
-Hello Ms. Mira, welcome.
[Mira] I'm here!
Laura, you have to choose the shoes.
I couldn't decide.
What is this? Who gave it to her?
My New Year's dress.
Help me out.
[panting]
There's no time for the dressing room.
I'm sorry.
Do you know how much time this takes?
-[Laura] Mira--
-[man 1] More light on five!
I'm sorry, I had a rehearsal
for New Year's Eve.
I couldn't get out of the square.
Mira, you're on call,
and you're getting paid for it, no?
[sighs] A contest on TV.
Don't be dramatic.
What is this?
Some kind of demonstration? Punishment?
-[Laura] A replacement.
-A replacement? For whom?
Sweetie, take it off.
We don't have much time.
We're going live soon.
-How much time left?
-[woman 2] I'll manage.
Four minutes.
She's sulking.
And why did you bring her here?
-Which shoes?
-These.
[man 2] Okay, are we ready?
All right, please go back to your places.
What are you looking at?
[man 2] Time to leave the set.
Please leave.
[breathes]
[Laura] Take your places!
-Let's start with two and three!
-[exhales]
[drumroll and fanfare playing]
[announcer] Telecontest.
[man 2] Camera one. Three…
Hello and welcome to the last
TV prize draw competition this year,
or even this millennium.
[man 1] Easy.
-Slowly. You hear me?
-[man 2] Mm-hm.
[man 2] Good evening.
[indistinct chatter]
[clock ticking]
[Mira] And now…
Stop!
And we have the name
of our potential winner.
Now a moment for me to focus,
so I don't misdial any numbers.
[phone ringing]
[Mira] And we're calling somewhere
far away, all the way to Sokołów Podlaski.
One more moment of patience…
[contestant] Yes, hello?
-Hello?
-[contestant] Hello? I'm here.
Good evening. This is Mira Kryle.
[contestant] How do you do?
Jadwiga Jeżewska.
[man 3] Get him out.
[Mira] Nice to meet you.
I understand you're watching us.
-[man 3] We're live.
-[contestant] Yes, of course.
[Mira] So, what am I doing now?
-[man 3] We're live.
-[contestant] Waving at me.
[man 3] Don't let him in.
-I'm waving at you. Good evening.
-[man 3] He's got a gun!
-[Mira] Unfortunately, I can't see that.
-[contestant] Halina! I won, see?
-[man 3] Duck!
-I'm sorry, we're…
[contestant] Hello?
[gunman] Don't move.
[Laura] Switch, don't show him.
Hold on Mira.
We're having technical difficulties here.
[gunman] Stop!
-Don't move!
-[contestant] Hello?
[Laura] Play a tape.
-Ladies and Gentlemen, I'm here--
-[man 4] We've been taken off air.
-…because I'd like to talk.
-[contestant] Did I win the car?
-To imagine…
-[Mira] What the fuck is this?
Jesus, Laura, is this some sort of joke?
-You must be crazy!
-Stop, I said!
[contestant] Because there are…
some stripes here.
They took us off air?
Hm.
-[contestant] Hello!
-[gunman] Turn it on.
Turn the cameras on! Make it work!
You hear me? Turn the cameras on!
[Mira] It's them in the control room.
[contestant] And now some fireworks.
You need to talk to them… upstairs.
[contestant] Hello? Can you hear me?
[breathing heavily]
Handcuff yourself to her.
[yelps]
[contestant] Hello, Miss Mira,
it's just that… I can't hear anything.
Miss Mira, stay calm.
-[yelps]
-[gunman] As tight as you can.
And… sit down!
Sit on your ass!
We're going live, get it?
[contestant] Who are you?
Hello?
Can you broadcast
on the main channel from here?
You can broadcast
to all of fucking Poland.
[contestant] Hello? Can you hear me?
Marek?
Are you recording?
Put some tapes in and record all cameras.
[man 4] You're sending someone?
Yes, all right…
[contestant] I could hear you
a moment ago, and now I can't again.
Hello?
Do what you have to give her that prize.
You won the grand prize.
[contestant] I won! See?
[chuckles] Well, Happy New Year!
All right, let's take it easy.
We're going live
unless you don't care about them.
[indistinct chatter]
Nowacki from Security.
Building E. E as in Echo.
-The guard room can direct you.
-Take the cuffs off and give them to me.
[Nowacki] We don't know how he came in.
Maybe he's specially trained.
-[gunman] Get a move on, take it off.
-Give me a minute.
Let me go.
[clattering]
[Nowacki] He didn't mention a ransom.
-[gunman] Hello!
-He wants to talk.
There's a microphone on the console.
You press the button…
This is totally not my job,
this kind of thing.
Armed assault.
We check IDs here.
[gunman] Hello?
Is anyone there?
Hello? Can you hear me?
[Mira] Laura? [clears throat]
Hello!
Is anyone there?
I actually don't know.
[man 3] Quiet! Quiet!
Hello? [mic screeching]
Hello? Well, you were in no hurry.
-[mic screeching]
-[Laura] You need to move to the center.
What?
[Laura] When I turn on the mics,
and you're there,
it creates this screeching noise.
-[gunman] Who am I talking to?
-[Laura] The producer.
What? I can't hear you.
Producer Laura Kołodziej.
Do you have any demands?
What is this about?
Let's stop playing games.
Games?
Because this is fun for you?
-This is fun?
-[Laura] No!
-Is this fun?
-[Laura] Not at all.
Can we speak normally?
[man 3] Don't approach the windows.
Don't provoke him.
[gunman] All right, we'll talk normally.
He's coming here!
Get out, all of you! Now!
He's coming.
[man 2] Faster.
That's the proper reaction.
Let's start over.
[speaking louder]
Let's start again! Slowly, yes?
First of all, turn off those lights
and turn on some normal ones.
-What are you doing?
-[light switch shuts]
All right.
Get ready for my live appearance.
[Laura] It's impossible.
There's a schedule.
All right. I'll make a call.
Stop!
[panting]
[sobbing] I'm sorry. I won't do it again.
I beg you. I won't do it… [crying]
[Laura] Just stay calm.
[Mira whimpering]
[Laura] Mira!
Sorry. I won't do it again.
[Laura] Sir,
please don't do anything to her.
Fucking hell!
[thuds]
[Mira] I'm sorry.
I won't do it again. I'm sorry.
[Laura] Please, sir,
don't do anything to her.
[gunman] Get up.
[Mira whimpering]
[Laura] Sir, please.
I can't do anything by myself here.
I need…
-Why do you want this? Tell me.
-I don't have to do anything.
[Laura] All right, how long?
A few minutes.
-[Laura] But what will you be doing?
-I don't know, singing.
I got eliminated from
A Chance for Success.
[Laura] All right.
All right, turn on whatever you need,
and let's go.
[Laura] I need time
to get a crew together.
A camera operator,
someone for sound and for lights.
Then get a move on.
[Laura] All right, I'm making a call.
Just stay calm.
I am calm.
[Mira sobbing]
[sniffles]
Get in the car!
[flashers blinking]
Are you in cahoots with him?
I don't understand.
What do you two want?
What do you want?
But Miss Mira,
I've been working here for two years.
Last winter, when your car broke down,
I helped you out. Don't you remember?
Then why aren't you doing anything?
You need to keep calm and do what he says.
[gunman] Can you make
external calls from this phone?
Zero. Then the area code.
[car door closes]
[exhales]
[flashers blinking continues]
Move over to your side.
Move over.
[phone dialing]
[ringing]
[man 5] Hello?
[gunman] Dawid?
Hi, it's me.
[Dawid] Shit,
you weren't supposed to call me.
[gunman] I know, I get it.
[Dawid] Fine, say why you're calling.
[gunman breathing heavily]
[Dawid sighs]
Fuck, say what this is about
and stop panting into the phone.
[gunman]
I just wanted to catch you before…
[Dawid] Catch?
[gunman] Just to send you my regards.
[Dawid sighs] You're crazy, really.
-I have to run, see you.
-No, wait. Wait. [hesitates]
[Dawid] Yeah?
Do you have a TV there?
[Dawid] TV?
Do you have a TV there or not?
[Dawid] Fuck, there is one.
Then watch it tonight.
[Dawid] What?
Sebastian?
Sebastian.
[announcer] Pessimists even claim
that on the first of January,
the banking system might collapse,
planes using computer navigation
might fall from the sky.
And in hospitals,
specialist equipment will stop working…
[medic] This is another thing
related to the Y2K effect.
Out of nerves, some apartments
were getting ready
almost for war conditions.
I saw piles of cans, packages of pasta,
boxes of candles, matches,
a supply of water kept in bathtubs,
pots and so on.
They claimed that something
would happen at midnight.
POLICE
[unsettling music playing]
Ready?
Yes.
I'm the primary, you support.
You'll be fine.
Who's in charge?
[man 1] That's right.
Fire fighters? I don't know.
They might be here already.
Will you check?
We need ambulances to run the operation.
Should we deploy?
[sighs] On New Year's fucking Eve.
[Mira whimpering]
[Mira] Laura, can you hear me?
[Mira breathing heavily]
Laura, please…
[Sebastian] Get out.
Get out!
[Mira] I have to call home.
I have a baby with a babysitter.
I should be home by now.
I was to take the baby to my mother.
I'm a single mother.
-You're not calling anyone.
-One call, please.
[Sebastian] You're not calling anywhere,
okay?
Who are you?
Someone who doesn't respond
to emotional blackmail.
[walkie-talkie static]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Sebastian] Where's the operator?
[Laura] We are looking for someone
brave enough to enter the studio.
Let's give people some entertainment.
After all, the viewers are waiting.
[phone rings]
Hello?
[man 1] Hi there, kid.
Congratulations,
beautiful entertainment. Well done!
Having fun? Is everything all right?
Listen, don't stress.
Put me on speaker.
I have a couple of words for Mira.
-Who's speaking?
-A fan from the crew!
Man, finally, something
is fucking happening in this studio.
Thank you very much.
Come on, listen, put me on speaker.
There's this big button there.
Put me through. Two words for Mira.
[on speaker] Mira?
Mira, wave to the camera
if you can hear me.
To show you can hear me…
Fucking hell, you're so dumb, aren't you?
I was wondering
if you'd fucking wave or not.
But without a smile?
For the viewers,
you have a fucking beautiful smile,
and what about your colleagues?
-Just fucking smile, won't you?
-[man 2] Do you recognize that voice?
-[man 1] Mira?
-No, I don't,
but he must be on TV grounds,
since he can see her.
Get the fuck out!
[swat 1] Did you get a look?
[officer] We're assuming
it's a live weapon.
The sniper is on position.
Just in case, the glass is thick,
hard to tell how the bullet will fly.
You talk to him, and we'll get downstairs,
two shots in the hinges and assault.
We blow the joint.
One of them might go down, but maybe…
All right, take it easy.
Just be ready,
and we'll start negotiating.
[indistinct chatter]
-Will you start?
-[officer] Yes. Excuse me.
[man 1] You know we've been making bets?
Piotrek, Karol, Andrzej, Lusia
bet that he would
blow your fucking brains out,
-but the rest think he has no balls--
-[hangs up]
[phone rings]
[Laura] Listen.
-It's the chairman for you.
-Excuse me, how do you use this?
Krzysztof Jedynak,
District Police Headquarters II Mokotów,
I'm listening.
This one here…
Hello. No, he's not here, I am.
[Laura]
…and this one you press only when talking.
[Jedynak] Are you trying to intimidate me?
Well, we're doing our job.
Are you ready?
-Yes.
-Then start.
Then make the call.
[Mira] I understand you all
are having a lot of fun there?
You tapped into the mix feed,
and you're having some fun.
Like we're a movie.
Should I wave?
Miserable bastards.
I mean, who even takes
a shift on New Year's Eve?
What's your name?
Grzegorz.
[officer] Hello, Sebastian.
My name is Piotr.
I'm here to help you handle this matter.
Where's the other lady?
[Piotr] Miss Laura is here next to me.
Together we'll be getting
a camera operator for you.
I want to see you. Turn on the light.
[Piotr] Sebastian, please,
put the gun down. It's not necessary.
Please, do not point it at me.
It stresses me out. I'm scared.
As you should be.
Turn that fucking light on.
[Piotr] Sebastian, stay calm, please.
Put down your weapon.
Then I'll come to you.
[uneasy music playing]
Turn off the light!
Who the fuck is that?
[Piotr] Sebastian, Please, don't do that.
-Put the gun down.
-Turn that light on!
-[Piotr] Put the gun down.
-Turn the light on!
[Piotr] I'm begging you, put the gun down.
Stay here.
[Piotr] You threaten
an innocent person with a gun.
[Mira whimpers]
[Piotr] Sebastian, please.
Put the gun down.
We can talk calmly.
[Sebastian] Turn the light on!
-Can we turn the light on?
-[officer 1] Alpha ready.
[Jedynak] Stay in position.
Turning on the light.
[officer 2] Beta ready.
[speaking indistinctly]
Sebastian,
we did what you wanted.
Can you show yourself?
-Did they turn it on?
-[Grzesiek] Yes.
-Yes?
Now, what do you see?
[Grzesiek] Um…
[Sebastian] What do you see?
A lot of people.
And they're aiming at me.
Balaclavas, get the fuck out of there,
you hear me?
Pull everyone back.
-[Sebastian] Get the fuck out!
-Wait.
[Piotr] Sebastian, I can't see you.
Please show yourself.
Get out of there! Everyone get out!
They're still there.
I don't know how many there are,
about ten, eleven.
How many?
[Grzesiek] Ten, eleven,
with automatic weapons.
[panting]
Um…
Get the police out of here, please.
Get the police out of here
so that nobody is harmed.
All right, let's pull back. Pull back.
[Piotr] We're doing what you asked for.
The police are leaving now.
[breathing heavily]
[Piotr] Sebastian, I can't see you.
[Sebastian] You, in the middle, get up!
That's what I thought. Get the fuck out.
We're going live,
so we can finish this quickly.
The car.
The car! Grzesiek.
Push the car over here.
[panting]
Put it in neutral.
Mira, move the cameras.
I can't see him.
Where is he?
Come here, inside the car.
-Talk. Get him out--
-Quiet,.
Sebastian, I understand
the sight of the police disturbed you.
I'm very sorry you got upset.
-Give us a moment to do what you asked.
-You have ten minutes!
[Piotr] Thank you very much.
[beep]
Come on, lend me your watch.
[flashers blinking]
[breathing heavily]
I'll give it back.
[Jedynak] We need to also be ready
to let him go live.
[Laura] And if he shoots Mira or the guard
in front of the TV audience,
or blows his brains out,
or screams, "gas the Jews,"
or does the Hitler salute?
Then we interrupt him or take him off.
No, it's not possible.
That's the end of it.
You don't do things like that on TV.
[indistinct chatter]
And even if you could,
it's not a decision you or I can make.
[unsettling music playing]
[Jedynak] They're interrogating
that Dawid guy that he called.
So far, we know the little shit
has no criminal record.
He studied at a technical university,
but he dropped out.
He lives with his mother.
-Only child.
-[Piotr] That's all?
That's all they managed to get out of him,
but they're still with him.
[Lena] Two minutes.
He almost looks like an operator now.
[Piotr] I really don't recommend this.
-We'll just get another hostage.
-[officer] Beta is inside.
[Piotr] Let's do our job.
[Jedynak] Make sure they show him
how to use that camera.
[phone ringing]
Well? What do you mean he insists?
Then come on, bring him here but fast,
with the siren on.
Thirty seconds.
[Sebastian] Time is up.
[Piotr] We managed to get you an operator.
Then where is he?
[Piotr] He's already on his way.
We are doing as you asked.
Could you let one of the hostages go?
No, you haven't done anything yet.
You haven't done anything yet.
Where the fuck are we? On TV?
There's nobody on site? How much longer?
[Piotr] It's not that easy.
Today is New Year's Eve.
Everyone is busy with the concert.
I'm fucking tired
of your fucking New Year's Eve. Get out.
[Piotr] Sebastian, you have a gun.
You need to understand
people are afraid to come into the studio.
Get out. In front of the cameras.
I'm sorry, but… I… just can't take hearing
one more word about an operator.
Nobody has to come in.
I can set it all up myself.
[Piotr] Miss Mira, I didn't hear you.
[Sebastian] Can she operate this?
Is that true?
[Piotr] I don't know what Mira can do.
And I don't know what this man can do.
I don't know who he is. I've been…
I've been working here for 15 years.
I can…
explain everything to you. Can I?
They just need to put it on the air.
Go on.
Grzesiu, take a chair
and sit on the stage.
Miss Mira?
Do you need anything?
[Mira] When the camera is on,
you can see a red light.
We have…
four cameras.
One… wide, never mind. Two…
close-up. Three…
you're in down to the knees.
-Stop her somehow.
-[Piotr] How?
[Mira] This is the zoom.
There on the handle there's focus.
You just can't sit the way he does
because it looks bad, unprofessional.
Sit up straight.
Sit properly.
When they turn on the lights and cameras,
you might choke up a little bit.
It's a lot of pressure.
You need to be ready for that.
[inhales, exhales]
All right, then put me on the air.
[Jedynak] We'd have already been in there.
We'd have him.
All this "I don't recommend that…"
What the fuck do you actually recommend?
-First of all, to stay calm.
-[Sebastian] Put me on the air already!
Then answer him.
It's not that easy.
Sebastian, there's nobody here
who can make that decision.
Sebastian, put the gun down. I beg you.
The safety is off.
It could go off at any moment.
-I'm begging you.
-Will you find someone now?
[Piotr] Please, at least
put the safety on. There's nobody here…
-Only the chairman can make the decision.
-Then get the chairman.
[Piotr] We're doing everything
to get him as fast as possible.
-Please, put the gun down.
-How long till he gets here?
[Piotr] This could take a while.
He's not in Warsaw. He's on his way.
[whispering] Fuck.
Sebastian,
there's a way out of this.
Please, put the gun down.
Everything can go differently.
It's not too late.
Article 252
of the criminal code, section four.
"Who refrains from extortion
and frees the hostage is not punishable."
So, what? I should just lay down?
Give myself up?
Put the gun down. Yes.
[clicks tongue]
All right, but that's section four, right?
What about the other three?
[Piotr] Please, put the gun down.
Let's hear the first one.
[Piotr] "If someone takes a hostage,
it's punishable by three years in prison."
-The second one is irrelevant.
-[Sebastian] Let's hear the second.
"If it's accompanied by cruelty
towards the hostage,
from three to 25 years."
But remember section four.
"If someone refrains from extortion
and releases the hostage,
they are not punishable."
I'm giving you a solution.
It's still not too late, Sebastian.
[inhales, exhales]
[Piotr] Sebastian.
[sighs]
[Piotr] Sebastian, let's get back
to our conversation.
We've managed to get so far together.
[exhales]
Good, keep it going.
[Piotr] "Whoever refrains from extortion
is not punishable".
But you need to release a hostage.
[sniffs]
Sit down.
Then choose which one you want.
Choose!
I have a child.
How do you know he doesn't?
Do you?
I do.
[Sebastian] Decide!
[humming]
[Piotr] I hope that everyone
gets to go home safely today.
Yeah, especially me.
Decide. Choose one.
[gun cocks]
-[Sebastian] Ten, nine…
-[Piotr] Don't do this. Put the gun down.
-[Piotr] It's almost… We were almost…
-…eight, seven…
Sebastian, Mira, let Mira go.
-Please, let Miss Mira go.
-Sit down.
Sit.
[Piotr] Sebastian, you promised
you would let one person go.
No, I didn't promise anything.
I just asked you to choose.
I'm done talking to you.
That's it.
Keep quiet until the chairman arrives.
-Sebastian, I'm very sorry that…
-Keep quiet until the chairman arrives!
What now?
So?
-We wait.
-How long?
Until he calms down.
I don't have a magic word.
I'm asking how long.
We might welcome the New Year here.
You must be kidding.
We're digging in. The guy is smart.
What are you doing here? Get out!
I see, he does what he wants with you.
-And that guy keeps thanking him.
-Those are procedures.
The perp needs to think he's on top,
in control.
But he can't really be in control of you.
-I can see Piotrek can't handle it.
-He had a tough time.
-When?
-Early December.
But he trained me.
He knows what he's doing.
Wasn't he the one dealing
with that gas tank in Wola?
Murder-suicide,
the guy blew up himself and his family?
Fuck.
-[officer] We have a guest at the front.
-I'm coming.
What's going on?
We're getting ready. Just a moment.
[announcer 1]
This is a one-of-a-kind evening and night,
like nothing you've ever experienced,
or ever will again.
Ladies and Gentlemen, congratulations
on not going anywhere tonight,
that you stayed home in front of your TV
because thanks to that, you…
He should speak plainly to the miners
who are gathered here.
In just a moment…
[announcer 2] Coming up,
the beginning
of our New Year's celebrations…
the band, Boney M!
[crowd cheering]
-[Jedynak] Please, have a seat.
-[man] Yes.
[Piotr] On these monitors you can see
what's going on in the studio.
Like we talked about.
You can talk about
any current issues you want.
Don't worry, I'll be here next to you,
and we can stop any time.
[man] Yes.
Sebastian.
[Piotr] Sebastian, can you hear me?
There's someone
who would like to talk to you.
[Sebastian] I'm not talking to you!
He's not from the TV station.
He had nothing to do with it, you hear me?
Nothing at all. He knew nothing.
Dawid,
don't tell them anything, you hear?
You hear me, Dawid?
They have nothing on you, don't worry.
You'll be fine.
-Can you hear me?
-Sebastian… [clears throat]
Sebastian, it's me.
Can you hear me?
It's me.
[exhales]
[chuckles]
No way, I don't believe it.
Show yourself.
It's me.
That's perfect.
I see you've put on weight.
You're doing well.
Go home, you hear me?
Go home.
You don't need any of this.
I just want to help you.
[Sebastian] Whose idea was this?
God, the Father, spoke from the speaker?
Wrong address, I'm afraid.
Dad, go home, I beg you.
You don't need… Go back home…
Leave me here.
You don't have to be like that, really.
You already told me. We know.
What did I say?
What did I tell you?
Where's Mom?
[father] She didn't want to.
When they came for me,
I thought something had happened to you.
And what did you feel?
What am I supposed to say now?
[Sebastian hesitates] Say what you feel.
Sebastian, we can stop this conversation
anytime you want.
[Sebastian] No, let… let me.
We'll have a conversation.
Can we?
Um…
[father] But let's talk normally.
All right? Normally.
Normally?
Did you take a look around you?
What do you mean normally?
How can I say this?
I'm kind of busy right now.
[father] Listen,
they are recording everything in here.
What do you need this for?
I don't know, as a… keepsake?
What keepsake?
[exhales]
Please. Just walk away.
[clicks lips]
I can't.
Everyone here, you see…
came here for me.
The chairman is coming here.
I will be on live TV.
What? Aren't you proud of your boy
that he'll be on TV?
[father] That's enough.
[Sebastian] No? You can sit down
with your family in front of the telly.
Stop it.
Just stop showing off.
Stop clowning around.
You showed off enough.
-Excuse me.
-Fuck!
Leave that. Get out!
Get out! Move back!
Everyone, move back, I said.
Just take it easy, okay?
Very good.
-May I?
-Yes.
Son…
I'm here.
[hesitates]
Where were you when they came for you?
[father] We were with our neighbors
for New Year's Eve.
Listen to me.
Let those people go,
the ones behind you, I mean…
I already talked to the policemen.
You can go to a hospital and…
You want to lock me up in a hospital?
Hey, tell me, how is your Dorotka doing?
Must be pissed?
What do you want?
Is this about me?
No. Try to imagine that this one time,
it's not about you.
Then what is this about?
Don't you know
what your mother is feeling right now?
You should leave mom out of this.
[father] They came to her first.
Your mother said
that she doesn't want to see
how her…
her only son…
Well, finish the sentence.
Or should I do it for you?
Do you really have no shame at all?
[Sebastian]
I have nothing to be ashamed of.
Really?
Did he stutter like that before now?
And on the air, live,
will you stutter like that as well?
-I mean, we have to stop it.
-[Jedynak] Quiet.
[father] What? Did you think of that?
What happens when you start
stuttering on TV?
And live?
Don't run away now.
Sebastian!
Have you forgotten already?
When we went to the clinic in…
um… to Warsaw?
He didn't say a word for six months!
And then training started,
something changed,
and the scanning speech began.
Did you forget that already?
"What did you eat, son?"
"I aaaaate…
aaa…
meeeat…
loaaaf. "
And you couldn't interrupt.
You had to calmly li… listen
until he was finished.
"What else did you eat? Tell me,
what else did you eat, son?"
"Iiii aaate aaaa saaalaaaad."
-"Aaaand I draaank the compoooote."
-Shut your face!
Sit down. Sit down. He's bottled
that up inside for a long time.
So, what? Now you're gonna s… sleep well?
[Sebastian] Uh…
A… And do you r… remember this?
[sobs]
F… first
pancake…
Fuck!
[breathing shakily]
[stutters]
F… fii… first pan…cake… i-i-is…
Always spoiled.
Let me fucking finish for once!
[Sebastian stutters]
Fi… Fiiirst pancake…
[exhales]
[voice trembling]
First pancake is always spoiled.
Remember?
You remember.
You'll like it in prison.
[crying]
You hear me?
In prison they'll…
In prison,
they'll knock
that sick lifestyle out of you
when they fuck you in the ass!
They'll knock that out of you in prison,
you'll see!
[crying]
[Lena] Come with me, this way.
-[Laura] How could you let that happen?
-Let what happen?
Stop talking to me like that. Understand?
See what happened?
Daddy came and the little shit crumbled.
He won't keep stringing us along.
[Piotr] You need to start listening
to my recommendations.
[Jedynak] It's my operation!
Didn't you ask to come here?
[Jedynak] Start controlling your emotions!
-[Piotr] We're both writing reports.
-[Jedynak] Report whatever you want.
[Piotr]
I don't want to talk to you anymore.
[Jedynak] Me neither.
The police came, started asking questions.
I had to see it for myself.
I thought maybe…
My father was very strict with me.
He had everything.
He quit university out of laziness.
What? Do you think I'm proud
that it turned out that…
That… it didn't work out…
My first time? That…
I always paid child support on time.
I was never late.
What can a 20-year-old know about…
children and life? Nothing, nothing.
"First pancake is always spoiled."
"First pancake is always spoiled,"
that's what I blurted out once
because he pissed me off.
You can see yourself
what kind of instigator he is.
I mean, every conversation
with him is some kind of…
[Lena] Do you think
your son could hurt someone?
I'm a little embarrassed by him now.
What were you asking? If what?
I asked if you think that your son
is capable of really hurting someone.
How should I know?
After all, I don't know that person.
We want money! Enough poverty!
[vocalizing]
We just feel like the people
of the last decade,
of the last millennium.
We've entered the new century.
We feel much older…
It's not difficult to say,
"We will give you more money."
It's difficult to say,
"We won't give you money."
Get up.
You're switching as I said.
You're in the chair now, kid, sit down.
Move the fuck to the other chair.
No discussion, I'm telling you.
What's going on?
You're the primary now.
-[Jedynak] Start talking to him.
-One moment.
No "one moment." We have no time, talk.
[exhales]
[switch turning on]
[Lena] Sebastian?
I wanted to apologize to you
for the situation with your father.
I admit that was a mistake.
He insisted on coming here.
We don't know you or him.
We shouldn't have done that.
[Jedynak] Where is he?
I also agreed to it.
That's why I'm apologizing, okay?
My name is Lena.
[Jedynak] Figure out where
the hostages are. I want to see them.
[Lena] Can you tell me how Miss Mira
and Mister Grzegorz are doing?
Miss Mira?
Mister Grzegorz?
We haven't seen you in a long time.
We understand you might not want to talk…
but we're just worried about you.
Maybe we could see you?
Can this be turned around?
[Lena] Something's happening.
There they are.
[Jedynak] Where is that?
Here?
That's it?
[Lena] Thank you.
But…
it would be easier for me to talk to you
if I could see your face.
No, I think you've had
a good enough look at me.
Is that not enough? You met my dad.
It's my turn to have a look at you.
There's more of you there.
Show yourself.
Where are you?
Come closer to the window.
[Laura] Here's the microphone.
You had your show,
now it's our turn to have a look.
-Can you see him?
-No.
[Sebastian] How are you feeling?
What are you looking at?
You like how you look?
Hm?
Well, what do you like the most
about yourself?
I don't know, I have big eyes.
[Sebastian] What don't you like?
Everything below that.
[Sebastian] What?
You don't want to be on TV?
Deploy. Full alert.
[Sebastian] You don't like that?
Everyone wants to be on TV.
Not me… I wouldn't want that actually.
-And you?
-[scoffs]
[Lena] It's about TV, right?
[scoffs]
Do you even watch it at all?
[Lena] Sometimes.
Sometimes.
Maybe if you did it more often,
you would know.
I would know what?
[Sebastian] Do you know how much time
our compatriots spend in front of the TV?
Four hours a day.
Four hours a day in front of the TV.
Do you know how much
you can do in four hours?
A lot of things.
Mm.
A lot.
And what would you do?
I don't know,
probably some typical activities.
I'd make myself dinner,
walk the dog.
[indistinct chatter]
And if it were your last four hours?
[whispers] Keep him talking.
I'd go to the tanning salon.
[laughs faintly]
Why are you laughing?
[Sebastian] No, you just…
You just surprised me.
Tanning salon.
[laughs] Your priorities are interesting.
Do you know people here
were taking bets about you?
[Sebastian] What did people bet on?
A lot of different things.
Mostly that… you were unemployed.
Or that you're a student
that was kicked out of university.
Maybe that you're a son of a farmer or…
that you're ill and…
they took your medication subsidy.
And what did you bet on?
That this is something personal,
or you wouldn't have called Dawid.
You wanted him to watch, didn't you?
I want to assure you
that he won't be in any trouble.
[Alpha leader] Full readiness.
Hostages on the left side in the center.
[Beta leader] Beta team ready, over.
I can feel this is something…
very important.
-Wait.
-Fucking hell.
Important. Bound to be important, right?
What's with this "important" talk?
It's important to me.
For you too. But not for someone else.
-[Lena] I understand--
-No, you don't understand!
Whatever I say to the camera,
people on the other side will believe.
-You know how that works.
-Move in. Go, go, go, go, go. Talk, talk.
-[Sebastian] What's happening?
-Sebastian, we have a sound malfunction.
[drilling]
[upbeat music playing]
Are you fucking mad?
Turn it off. You hear me?
You think I'm an idiot?
Do it, full volume.
Turn it off!
Relax, put your gun down. Please…
What if I have a fucking bomb?
[Lean] I'm sorry, could you repeat that?
I can't hear.
-[upbeat music continues]
-[drilling]
What? So many of you there
and nobody thought
to ask what I have in my bag?
-He's got a bomb.
-What do I say to him?
-Bomb. Evacuate. We're pulling out.
-What now?
-Evacuation.
-[Lena] That bag has complicated things.
-What's going on there?
-[alarm blaring]
[Lena] I have to go now.
-No, you're not going anywhere, stay.
-This is procedure, but I'll come back--
[alarm blaring]
[Sebastian] Lena!
[Jedynak] Designate a safe spot.
Lena, talk to me. Lena!
[alarm blaring]
Do something!
[Leonard Bernstein's "Symphony No. 2
The Age of Anxiety" plays]
[alarm bell ringing]
[officer] Attention, this is the police.
Please remain calm
and proceed to the exit.
The police will show you the way.
[knocking]
[Mira] Hello! Hello! Hello!
Hello! Stop!
[Bernstein's Symphony No. 2 resumes]
[officer] Attention. Please remain calm
and proceed to the exit.
This is an evacuation.
Who's gonna put you on the air now? Who?
There's no one… What are you looking at?
What the fuck are you looking at?
The entire building
has been fucking evacuated!
What now? [crying]
What?
Grzesiek. Grzesiek!
Grzesiek!
[Bernstein's Symphony No. 2 climaxing]
[audience clapping, cheering]
[Jedynak] There's the emergency exit,
please leave.
[indistinct chatter]
Are you sure that we can
establish communication here?
Yes.
All right.
Please leave the room. Secure the area.
Take these people outside.
[Sebastian] Grzesiek.
Hey! Grzesiek!
Is there any water here?
[objects clattering]
[Sebastian] I'm asking you.
[Sebastian] Grzesiek, get up!
Grzesiek.
-Hey.
-[Grzesiek] Hm.
[Sebastian sighs]
[panting]
[sighs]
-The entrance to the building is secure.
-Come.
Camera tracks ready?
All right.
Zdzisiu, the intercom is
the most important. Give me that.
Thanks.
[lighter flickers]
Hazard lights have slowed down.
[lighter flickering]
[Grzesiek] May I?
Sure, take it already.
[Mira sighs]
Could you… Could you stop…
pointing that gun at us?
I finished drama school.
I can play it all.
Then how did you end up here?
[Mira] Typically…
They had a blonde…
a brunette and a redhead,
they needed someone in-between.
[clears throat]
With charisma.
[static noise]
["Darkside" by Sonic Trip
feat. Ice-Tea playing]
Please remain calm.
I won't answer any questions
if you keep talking at the same time.
-[reporters clamoring]
-[reporter] Can we have a comment?
[festive music playing]
CAMERA 2 - CAMERA 3
[young man] In a week,
I'm going to join the army,
and after I come back,
I don't see any prospects here.
I'm going to leave this city.
I'm in school, and I don't know
what I'll do afterwards.
In a year, I finish school,
and I'll try to go to Germany.
I'm still in high school,
after that I'll go to university
or something,
then I'm going to Germany or…
getting out of this country.
I'll finish school and get out of here.
[Sebastian]
The main prize in the contest goes to…
Grzegorz.
[laughing]
I almost didn't make it here.
Today.
But I fucking made it.
Laura already brought…
Kasia?
-The weather girl?
-Miss Kasia. Miss Kasia Jaworska.
They even gave her my fucking dress.
You'd be sitting here with Kasia.
[chuckling]
-Stay close.
-[woman] I'll put a mic on you.
We'll catch them in the corridor maybe.
I don't really know, because if so, then…
I ate dinner, and I was just finishing,
reading something,
didn't hear anything.
Only later I found out…
You know, someone
threatened someone else with a gun.
Everything was ready for the millennium.
The Christmas tree, the tables,
and suddenly, this whole thing,
everything got moved.
His aggressive behavior, his kind of…
walking around like an animal in a cage,
which you could see on the cameras,
it all seemed like
he was a little unstable.
[Kasia] What did this man want to say
on New Year's Eve for the cameras?
It must have been a desperate act.
It must be something important
to take this kind of step.
[indistinct chatter]
[uneasy music playing]
[Lena] Sebastian? Can you hear me?
[Laura] Please try again.
Sebastian?
Good evening, Andrzej Kostecki,
the network chairman.
Was this your idea?
Great.
-Miss Mi--
-Who's in charge, where is the commandant?
-Miss Mira?
-[Andrzej] Which gentlemen did I talk to?
-[Jedynak] Me.
-Mister Grzegorz?
Can you hear me?
Sebastian?
-[Piotr] No connection.
-[Lena] Nothing.
[Andrzej]
I want to know what the situation is.
-[Piotr] In a moment. Be quiet.
-We have to.
It's the chairman.
[Lena] Sebastian, can you hear me?
-No, they still can't hear me.
-[Piotr] Nothing.
Sebastian?
[Sebastian] We hear you. We hear you.
So, you do have a signal.
[Lena] Yes, I can see and hear you.
I'm sorry that it took so long.
Do you need anything?
Water, food, medicine?
No, you can get me the chairman.
He was so outspoken
when he entered the studio. Let him talk.
I can talk to him.
[Sebastian] Go on, Kostecki.
I don't think we have a choice.
Please, sit down.
[Sebastian] Is he shitfaced?
He came straight from a New Year's party,
and you're afraid to let him talk?
-[Andrzej] May I?
-[Lena] Yes.
-[Andrzej clears throat]
-Hello?
Hello. This is Andrzej Kostecki.
Because of the bomb we had
to evacuate the entire building.
We are in the next building.
Mm-hm. You have a signal,
and everything's working. Can we start?
Because we were waiting just for you.
[Andrzej] Hmm… Well, we have to finish
all technical aspects.
[Sebastian] Be quick
because you don't have much time.
I'm going on after the president.
Do you know when he's supposed to finish?
Well… we don't know how long
the president's speech will take.
Then find out!
They do know.
It's pre-taped.
Andrzej, right?
Right.
[Sebastian] Listen, Andrzej,
stop fucking with me. All right?
Because you don't have much choice.
It's the broadcast or them.
But I can't make that decision alone.
Why the fuck wouldn't you?
-[Andrzej] I'll make a call and--
-Then what are you there for?
-[Andrzej] Stay calm.
-Why the fuck were we waiting for you?
What are you trying to pull?
-Good evening, Mister Andrzej.
-[Andrzej] Good evening, Miss Mira.
[Mira] I would really like to remain calm,
but I'm just losing my nerve.
[Andrzej sighs] Yes, Miss Mira,
please trust me. Everything will be fine.
[Mira] I'm trying.
[Mira]
I understand everything, you know that.
[inhales]
I would just like to know what's going on.
Miss Mira, please stay calm.
These are police procedures.
Well then, they fucking suck!
Fuck,
these procedures are shit.
You left us here completely… alone.
Do you know what that feels like?
I would just like to know
if anyone there decided,
"We're all getting the fuck out of there
and leaving Mira behind?"
Has anyone thought about me?
-Do you know what's it like to be…
-Miss Mira…
…completely alone?
[Andrzej] Miss Mira, stay calm.
We are all thinking about you.
We care, really. Please remain calm
and don't get hysterical.
[exhales]
All right.
[sniffs]
Or, I can just say fuck it all.
[footsteps moving]
Where has she gone?
[line tone calling]
Hi, Monika, this is Mira Kryle.
[Monika] Hi. At least we can
talk on New Year's Eve.
Where are you partying now?
-The concert or…?
-[Mira] Listen…
-Turn it off.
-[Mira] I'm calling on business.
-Turn that off.
-I don't control it.
Turn that fucking thing off.
Who do you work for?
-[Mira] There is a hostage situation…
-Please just… fucking hell.
-[Monika] Have you been drinking?
-[Mira] No, I'm not drunk.
-He's next to me.
-[Jedynak] Who is she calling?
[Monika] What are you talking about?
-The competition.
-[Mira] Call whoever you want.
Everyone's here.
I bet they're listening. Andrzej's here.
[sighs]
You're the first one I called.
Will you take it?
She called because she's hysterical.
I'm not going to the parking lot.
Tell them it's going well.
We're just trying to deal with it.
[Andrzej] How is it going well?
-Arrest her. I know where he lives.
-[Jedynak] For what?
[Andrzej] I don't know. Lack of
a fire extinguisher. Think of something.
Andrzej Kostecki, yes?
Yes, I was just talking to him.
[phone rings]
Can't you block that
through the TV council?
[Mira] Wait.
It will be live but an interview.
What do you say?
Eh… Decide.
[phone ringing]
[different phone ringing]
-[Monika] Give me one moment.
-[Mira] All right.
[Monika] Can I call you back?
-[Mira] Call main switchboard, then 501.
-[Monika] Sure.
[Mira] Thanks, Monika. I'm waiting.
Fuck. I hope it will be worth it.
[sighs] If I were in your place, I'd have
started shooting a long time ago.
[Lena] Sebastian, you've got it,
you hear me?
Sebastian, you're going live.
With everything, sound…
and video, you hear me?
We're preparing the live broadcast.
Just one more moment of patience,
all right?
Miss Laura… will walk you
through the technical details.
For the fifth, time we're meeting
on New Year's Eve.
But for the first time,
we are meeting in such a unique moment,
on the cusp of the symbolic year 2000.
This kind of occasion happens once…
Mister Grzegorz,
could you move it so I can see the face?
I can see the gun.
[President]
…counting time from the birth of Christ.
Today we're building
a free and secure Poland.
[Laura] A bit closer,
but don't cut the top of the head.
[President] …and stable.
[Laura] Sebastian,
could you take off the cap?
I can't see your eyes.
[President] …caring about its citizens.
Ladies and gentlemen…
[Laura] Thank you.
G-Grzegorz, c-could you move the TV?
I would like to see myself.
[sighs]
I need to powder your face.
You're all sweaty. How long?
[Laura] Two minutes.
Right after the speech,
we'll put up a screen saying,
"We interrupt this broadcast,"
and you can go.
How long should my announcement be?
-[Laura] Two, three sentences.
-I need to comb your hair.
Something neutral like,
"We interrupt this broadcast
for a special message," right?
[Laura] Yes. Concise.
One minute, 40 seconds.
[President] The last day of the year
is always special.
[Laura] Will you let him on the air?
It's your job to make sure
we can see and hear it.
It's part of your responsibility.
[President]
…not just at the past 12 months…
Excuse me.
[President] …but all the passing years
of our own lives,
our parents' and our children's.
[Laura] Kołodziej.
Let's synchronize, okay?
[President] Each one of us approaches
this occasion with humility…
[Mira] Can we check my mic?
One, two, three, four, five.
-[Laura] Put it higher.
-[Mira] Higher?
One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten.
One, one, one, one, one, one.
One, one, one, one.
[Laura] All right.
One minute.
Fix your hair at the back.
-[Mira] The back?
-[Laura] Mm-hm.
[Mira] Just two and three?
Because my shoes are untied.
[Laura] Don't worry.
Two is the main one.
Forty-five seconds.
[Mira] All right. [sighs]
I'll announce you,
then step down from the stand,
and you stand right where I was.
Okay?
-You can read from the cards.
-Please don't talk to me for a while.
[President]
I know not everyone has a chance
to spend this evening
the way they would like.
To those people especially
I send my warmest wishes
for luck and personal success.
In these wishes,
I remember all of those people,
who through their hard work
create our reality.
About working people,
entrepreneurs, scholars,
teachers, artists, doctors and nurses,
priests, local government workers
and community workers.
There's more and more of us in this world.
The recipe for success is to live wisely,
in harmony with the world,
in peace and friendship with others.
Let's remember the world
is not the property of those who govern,
or those who rule by force,
or those who make their fortunes,
-or those with the best education.
-[Laura] Hello?
-Turn it off, please.
-[President] It belongs to everyone.
Let's be happy to greet the 21st century.
It is a great challenge,
but also a great chance…
[Laura] You're live in 15 seconds.
[unsettling music playing]
[Laura] Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
[sighs]
Welcome to a special edition
of our program.
Mira Kryle, welcome.
There are moments for which even we,
the TV people, are not ready.
We interrupt our scheduled program
-to broadcast a special message…
-[Grzegorz] Nothing.
-[gasps] It's live. [moans]
-No, it fucking isn't. Come here.
-Sebastian, no.
-[Sebastian] You thought I wouldn't check?
-It's not on?
-No!
[Lena] Sebastian--
[thuds]
-Now!
-[thud]
[pants]
[Sebastian] The light!
Turn on the light!
Grzesiek, Mira, on the floor!
Mira, on the floor!
Mira!
-[thuds]
-[shouts]
[breathing heavily]
[grunts]
-[groans]
-[Lena] Sebastian, what's going on?
Fuck me.
[Mira] No!
[whimpering, crying]
Stop the assault. Turn the lights on.
-Did you know about this?
-[Jedynak] Do something.
[Andrzej] What are they doing?
What the fuck is this?
-[Jedynak] Get those people out!
-Quiet!
-What the fuck is this?
[screaming]
[Lena] Sebastian?
Please, tell me what happened, all right?
Grzegorz, take the first aid kit.
[Lena] Can you hear me?
Stay calm, please, tell me.
We have a doctor here. Can you hear me?
-[Grzesiek] Fucking hell! Empty!
-[whimpering]
[Lena] Miss Mira!
If…
[Grzesiek]
She needs to go to the hospital.
[Lena] If something's happened,
please tell me, okay?
[Mira whimpering]
[Lena] Sebastian, if you need a doctor…
-[Grzesiek] You hear?
-[sobbing]
This is your fault.
Sebastian!
This is your fault!
[clamoring]
Stay calm, please.
-Tell me what's happened, okay?
-[Sebastian] It's your fault!
I really don't know
what to say to him now.
-What are you doing?
-I'm going in.
-What will you tell him?
-[Jedynak] I'll improvise.
-My ass is on the line anyway.
-[Piotr] Who will be in command?
[Mira crying] Oh fuck, oh fuck, oh fuck.
[breathing heavily]
[man] Let him through.
[reporter] Film him. Film him.
Film him. Film him.
[moaning]
-[crying]
-[Sebastian] Mira, stay calm.
[stutters] I'm sure you have insurance.
You will get some money out of it.
-Mira.
-Get away from…
[crying]
[knocking]
-[Jedynak] I'm alone. I'm unarmed!
-Hands in the air.
[Mira moaning]
I've brought water.
Can I see Miss Mira?
I'll open this a little.
Slowly.
Oh fuck.
I'm going to crouch.
-[Mira whimpering]
-Everything will be fine. Take it easy.
[moaning]
[Jedynak] Listen.
It's all gone too far.
Let her go.
Let's do it like that: I'll take her,
and she's not your problem anymore.
And you still have someone left, right?
Take her.
[grunts]
-Easy. One more time.
-[screams, groans]
-[Mira] No, no, no, no!
-Fuck. Okay, take it easy.
[whimpering in pain]
I'm coming in. I have to come in.
-Stop. Stop, I said!
-[Jedynak] Check it out.
I don't have a gun.
I'm clean. Take it easy.
Lower your weapon.
I'll take a chair, all right?
-Okay, take it and fuck off, you hear?
-Will you help me?
[Sebastian] Help him.
[Mira gasps, breathes heavily]
-No, no, no!
-[Jedynak] Easy.
[Mira groaning intensely]
-[Jedynak] Take it easy.
-The step, watch out.
The step.
[Mira crying in pain]
[breathing heavily]
[Mira groaning]
What are you doing? Come here.
Come on fucking back.
[locking]
[panting]
Mira! Mira! Mira! Mira!
[reporters clamoring]
[Lena] Sebastian?
How is she?
[Lena] She's been taken to the hospital.
You have your gesture of good will.
[Lena] No, Sebastian, that…
That's not what it was supposed
to look like.
I don't want, and I didn't want anything
to happen to you.
You know you don't have
to go to prison, right?
[Sebastian] It might be a little late, no?
Something has happened.
No, listen to me. There's a way…
You know the law, right?
You might not be fully aware
of what is going on right now, right?
If they decide you're insane, Sebastian,
you'll end up in…
[Piotr] Stop, Lena, stop. Enough.
[Lena] Fuck!
Can't you see it?
-You crossed the line.
-What?
[Sebastian] Grzesiek, go home.
Go home to your wife and kids.
I'm sorry.
[Sebastian]
What the hell are you sorry for, man?
I don't have children or a wife.
Go already, go.
I beg you.
Thank you.
[slams door]
[breathing heavily]
[flickers]
[exhales]
[Andrzej] Sebastian,
this is Andrzej Kostecki, the chairman.
You had to know it wouldn't be so easy
to get on TV just like that.
And here I was thinking I could make it.
[Andrzej] You know
it really doesn't have to end like this?
Sebastian, you are smart, after all.
You can't let this opportunity
go to waste.
This might be your only chance.
We could get it on tape.
we still have people working here.
In front of the building,
there is a crowd of reporters.
It's all about you, about your story.
This might be a big deal.
For prime time.
But that, of course,
depends on what you say…
Sebastian.
Don't just think about yourself.
Think about all those young people
who would be inspired by you.
You understand?
We could still get something out of this
for your entire generation.
[sighs]
-So, what now, which camera? This one?
-Yes, that one.
[whispers] Are the tapes rolling in there?
Yes, they are.
Maybe you want to rehearse a bit?
[Sebastian] No need.
[Andrzej] Say what you feel to the camera.
That's it. And start when you're ready.
I am.
-No!
-Put down the gun! I'm begging you.
That isn't necessary.
Sebastian, please, don't do that.
[flicks]
[gun cocks]
[officer 1] Second hostage secured.
-Do we come in or wait?
-Permission to start the assault.
-[officer 2] How many are in position?
-[officer 3] Everyone ready to breach.
On the ground!
Lie down on the ground!
Don't resist, you hear?
[dramatic music playing]
[officer 4] Police! Away from the door!
Lie down on the ground!
Three, two, one!
[firing]
[indistinct chatter]
[shatters]
[clamoring]
Cover the cameras!
[officers speaking indistinctly]
[Lena] Do something.
[Laura] Out of the way!
Come with me!
-Quick
-Run.
Come with me.
[officer 5] Tongue.
Show me your tongue! Cough!
-Harder!
-[Sebastian coughs]
[breathing heavily]
[grunts]
[Laura] We're recording! We're recording!
We're recording!
We're moving out. Please leave.
[officer 6] Leave that camera alone!
We're moving.
-Come on, you fucker, no sleeping.
-Let's go, no sleeping.
[dramatic music continues]
[man] I'd like to knock on the doors
of your homes.
Inside. Head down.
Can we clean this place up now?
[shutter clicking]
[police siren wailing]
["Freed From Desire" by Gala playing]
♪ My love has got no money
He's got his strong beliefs ♪
♪ My love has got no power
♪ My love has got no fame
He's got his strong beliefs ♪
♪ My love has got no money
♪ Want more and more ♪
♪ People just want more and more ♪
♪ Freedom and love ♪
♪ What he's looking for ♪
♪ Want more and more ♪
♪ People just want more and more ♪
♪ Freedom and love ♪
♪ What he's looking for ♪
♪ Freed from desire
Mind and senses purified ♪
♪ Freed from desire ♪
[vocalizing]
♪ My love has got no money
He's got his strong beliefs ♪
♪ My love has got no power
♪ My love has got no fame
He's got his strong beliefs ♪
♪ My love has got no money
♪ Want more and more ♪
♪ People just want more and more ♪
♪ Freedom and love
What he's looking for ♪
♪ Want more and more ♪
♪ People just want more and more ♪
♪ Freedom and love
What he's looking for ♪
♪ Freed from desire
Mind and senses purified ♪
♪ Freed from desire ♪
[vocalizing]